acaiberrystudies.com 2013-06-04

# Privacy Policy

## AcaiBerryStudies.com Respects Your Privacy.

Nothing is more important to AcaiBerryStudies.com than protecting the private information of visitors to our site. Below you'll find information about our commitment to ensuring the privacy of your personally identifiable information (such as your full name, address, email address, telephone number and/or other identifying information).

## Gathering and Use of Information

AcaiBerryStudies.com will never willfully disclose any personally identifiable information about our online audience to any third party without first receiving the user's permission. We do not collect personally identifiable information from our visitors other than what is supplied to us on a voluntary basis.

Visitors to AcaiBerryStudies.com may voluntarily supply certain personally identifiable information in connection with:

  * **(1.)** contest or sweepstakes registration
  * **(2.)** subscription registration for sites or services which require subscription (such as email newsletters)
  * **(3.)** requests for membership information. In addition, personally identifiable information is voluntarily provided in connection with certain content submissions, community postings (i.e., forums or bulletin boards), comments and suggestions, or voting.

AcaiBerryStudies.com may use such information only for conducting the activities stated above and for internal marketing and promotional purposes. The extent of such use is always explained at the time a site visitor provides such information. If the visitor does not want this information collected and used by us for the disclosed internal purposes, the visitor is given an opportunity to 'opt-out.' Our visitors need to recognize, however, that if they select to 'opt-out' they may not be eligible for certain activities for which the personally identifiable information is needed (such as contests, etc.).

## External Links

AcaiBerryStudies.com is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information. 

## Log Files

Like many other Web sites, AcaiBerryStudies.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. None of this log file tracking is linked to any information that personally identifies you.

## Acceptance of the AcaiBerryStudies.com Privacy Policy Terms and Conditions

By using this site, you signify your agreement to the terms and conditions of this AcaiBerryStudies.com Web Site Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, please do not use the site. Your continued use of the AcaiBerryStudies.com Web Site following the posting of any changes to these terms shall mean that you have accepted those changes. If you have any questions or concerns, please contact us at anytime.
